[Music]
yo yo yo
but up periscope periscope it should be
shared on Twitter now we're so chicken
yeah check us actually share a Twitter
the first time I saw Salt Lake's
everywhere
Salt Lake Sarah we're all right this is
where we get all our songs did we just
saw lights we probably imported probably
environmentally safe
hi genders
Jenner's gender attendings yeah you guys
it didn't drive nearly as well in Nevada
because Nevada paints lanes weird but
now that we are in Utah they know how to
build roads in Utah Utah you for Utah
they hang on to change lanes they will
you for your club you for Utah Utah
where you think that
shut up
driving this driving super well
we were just on the phone with so we're
like the away team
none of us are wearing red shirts
because welcome to survive
yeah if you missed the periscope the
floor it was boggy it is a mistake in
our periscope yesterday we said the
t-shirts we're gonna be $20 but I looked
up how much low peep was charging for
t-shirts and he was charging 30 so we're
charging 30 yeah is there one of those
shirts right now yeah weirdest too early
we got asked by some guy at a gas
station what we were what we were a
demonstration unity we showed them where
- music yeah he was like when you get
this
it's working for self-driving cars
that'll be the big thing yeah selling
cars out this big thing like I would
call us out for saying San Francisco
yeah you're talking to like someone from
Wendover Nevada baby I've never been
more happy to be in Utah
[Music]
yeah we do rich my penis love us love us
no we're not violating FMVSS anymore
yeah there was a violation that's why I
changed it yeah
we listen to regulate respect authority
it's pretty nice you guys by the way
like watch every farm clip my seatbelt
look at that so Center is good a little
bit the rav4 is a little bit higher than
the other cars so we're trying to the
whole crew to try to fix this in
software right now
but all this feels so much better than
Nevada yeah and the man at the right
lane was
four times as thick as they have it was
there was a probability promised and
didn't mention that
Carter if you're listening that's the
word yeah what was happening is the
right lane and a much higher probability
than the left and that's why the
straights
maybe that was even affecting their game
but yes we want to stop at one of these
Salt Lake outcroppings touch the salt
yeah you can touch it it won't burn you
no no but but I think you can even take
something with you but if you go to
White Sands National Parks you cannot
take the whites and they'll search your
car on the way out
take the green apparently they had a
problem like whites and by divers
somebody how many Skokie's have got 250
oh good see when you put it on Twitter
they all come yeah oh it was the M&M
before about disappointment
that'd be good name for an album
disappointment yeah
let's cheer disappointment
there's about say yes right we got the
honest
the creator but a second album
is like that what kind of star support
is your seat no mine's baby yeah what
clean me up trim what is it we were
talking about we don't really like this
part the Civic is so many heated seats
in the back
Oh like we're
on 3G
always on 3G too
don't try to do it to do I have it will
end interval to eat yeah I think they're
Department I mean yeah t-mobile didn't
pay the Salt Lake tower feet
there's more of those out fronts
the speed limit is 80 miles an hour here
too
any questions filly's for softness but
we're getting but wouldn't be happening
yeah you gotta come to a Midwest Midwest
is where we're doing to her stop
those stories so like so Joseph Smith
used to hanging out was in Pennsylvania
yeah it's like middle of Pennsylvania
and they were they were being very
intolerant of his boots
so like Moses he might have trapped out
here he discovered the most beautiful
saw legs and founded solid city which is
actually really especially pretty nice
so like think it's all exciting yeah
well you're gonna see once we go further
east of Salt Lake City you'll see if the
place of God is nice and softly scented
I'm not going to name names and offend
anyway
someone's things I like soy city's dr.
bit what is it kind of say it's time
dude that that last to manage it what is
up with that fake tree
three like that
what it's all exactly
maybe one of me with some GM engineers
in Detroit not this tour do we want to
be with local news outlets absolutely
wanna meet with ya local news outlets if
you're watching your back come with
Danny I send an email I would love to be
on a morning show shows radio we're cool
radio - you know the kind of morning
showing like four people sit around like
talk I'm down cup of coffee yeah I
love that
did we try to do battle Mountain yeah we
did battlefront now
yeah stuff yeah I got some good shot
like this
this is a scene from a Kiki film yes it
should be I'm doing it excellent
excellent job let's get that good film
see is a dinky film it's not a geek road
trip
great video killed the radio starts you
guys remember that song yeah
good filming thank you
first music video it
is that
nice salt back there by the stop if you
rub it on your skin or something like as
a bad work hard to purify that salt
oh the other chick Jessie from Saved by
the Bell starting showgirls
a five million dollar budget - something
to be nc-17 moving quasi-pornographic
given with Jessie takes you might have
had a math problem but I don't slander
her so
all those Tesla's oh wait supposed to
stop - maybe we can get my mind ready
yeah it's like a mall x-man look a try
the autopilot we'll check the check wait
screech did a sex tape - it's on
Wikipedia no way 2006 diamond directed
and released his own sex tape
Keith Street saved by the smell that's
Karen's a bad name is really terrible
but there was a stunt double that
performed in the sense that he just
directed
this is weird really we speedometer
check next five miles let's try our
sarong and our speedometers really wrong
45 seconds I can begin a stopwatch here
you guys we're at 77 get the stopwatch
on yeah should be going 80 according to
we set my set speeds are you going to
our yawn so we're gonna see who's more
correct Ian or Toyota
Aeon it was some signs that say
something about a speedometer check so
you think it's these yellow markers we
should signs that tell us what to do
and they never consult these roses like
serious Oh y'all ready I don't think we
were on the scope was charity overturn
like they just had like to slid off I
just think the road was that ice but
it's catchy with semi-trucks like they
flipped over and then the cab was upside
down yeah yeah virtually Chris I think I
would plan on it being a note for now
yeah we'll see we'll see we'll see how
that we'll see how the first step so
we'll see sure oh yeah yeah forty
t-shirts five of them are reserved for
people who've been helping us out in 35
t-shirts for sale yeah I think we have
eleven Aeons for sale eleven eleven
probably some tan in case our young
hoodies
just so we came to our house to buy a
hoodie we give a discount she walks in
person this and that was 100 bucks that
I lost him a bet
let's talked about the last periscope
right space they've got a pay attention
it's like a sequel references back
references we should back reference to
all the periscopes you gotta watch them
all hey there's someone out there
okay we're kind of like here I don't
know I think our periscope is live
location share if somebody out there in
the world can figure out where the next
stop is to stop it yeah awesome exactly
we see the mile four sign then we're
gonna see the mile five sign that we
expect to be 45 seconds right how well
did he yawns keep speed
come up on this truck this truck I'm
gonna hit this truck
virtually Chris has watched every
periscope in full
very same for a new episode yeah episode
4 is coming up oh no no here's the sign
okay the red restarted ready don't
this up Eddie go
okay yeah that's so we sing mile five it
should be 45 seconds yeah we didn't
start the stopwatch the right time right
you don't really give us enough power
right now to buy for pudding that the
young to be honest the Honda Civic still
works the best but the future probably
is Toyota the rav4 does not work as well
as the same yes yeah we're all a little
disappointed by this but no he'll get
better
we've got a lot of time to tune the
Civic it may be good might despite my
speedometer saying 84 yards keep speed
please show the scope is the Toyota
speedometer and see what a scam it is
can you see it it's really a huge scam
pile over it's five over
like this says eat this is actually
correct this says 84 you guys know why
they do this right there we go we said
that in the first one can we have new
material make you go slow we're gonna
chauffeur
we're gonna shield for Dan Carlin's
hardcore history we're learning about
the goals
Cesar was really really documented
everything oh my god she's our Caesar
what they say about Caesar is like
Caesar just like thought and talked like
four times faster than a normal person
yeah Caesar didn't everything the man
was absolute
but you so he was military leader that
means name
yeah it's definitely it's smelly Hey
look open file it works the snow that's
anchor all those people when during
inclement weather good I don't like gas
truck this shot is so
I don't like passing trucks yeah Debra
moment which is always feels closer
yeah well it was also a really
unsettling to see three trucks flipped
over her yeah I know right right
we were thinking knockout gas and then
we start to smell something actually we
thought knockout gas but we started to
smell something think I'd be an open
palette if we had stolen one of those
tests of model axes you know
Oh No hey there's scope these haven't
been good at figuring out where they can
stop the salt
yeah you guys we should boost I was
gonna have him living with Toyota manual
it's snowing be at 52 a one of them can
look at Christmas man Sasha it looks
like my lungs okay I love this weather
what are we trying to figure out we're
trying to figure out where we can stop
to pull over you can see our our
location but maybe not
we're do this we're like oh they can't
see a location yeah so they do they see
kind of like an area we can pull over
stop some rest stop or whatever it's bad
now
we'll start seeing the Great Salt Lake
but that wasn't even a great great
thingy on Jill bit the Ebro used to be
where daddy's to play sport that we love
jailbreak jailbreak our back our
when we buy it you know what you
know what there's two types of people in
the world assholes and hypocrites
guys I'm not a hypocrite imagine we were
streaming 360 video yet imagine we had
an Andy Rubin essential phone samsung
chill man it's like Tom Schiller Twitter
Wow coming up trunk
you know what's really good on this guy
like when you're in a hearse someone's
driving by you and it tells it beeps at
you if you're back in the Joe it's great
be like yeah that's like a 360 Canada
three cigarettes go to but like
someone's dress speeding by you you're
trying to back out of your drive to Tom
her name is autumn because it just looks
so great - OH well Wayne mentions
two-tone of a song
Wow let's go what is that it's like an
apron
steel frame Oh pilot go through the snow
yeah this is a rav4 going faster less
afraid of all the signage is up more
fruit of the road
I'm so yeah this system just don't know
what to do about like slippery roads or
anything this car does have traction
control so that is nice
yeah I've tracked into trouble starts
going left ooh I love to slow down guys
go faster tires
better read the comments I love there's
not many comments Tommy
still waiting on you guys put this salt
lake's yeah we're gonna stop you get it
out with your scopes notice all this
there's an antelope island Wow I like
Juggalo island here's a comment okay
Great Salt Lake Park is about 50 minutes
away from where we're at
great pay money to get in there here's
another comment thank you guys this is
great dude jailbreak Tesla we would have
jumping those ones that we saw on the
side of the road that would literally we
stumbled upon
search you for Salt Lake and marijuana
don't bring marijuana to Utah kids wait
for Colorado don't work to Utah what's
your top choice yo I love them Apple
disgusting the RV's disgusting otherwise
and always end up getting much of
prospects
Oh Stingo kenick hope let's turn to
struggle things like state that Lane is
a little hard to see
put some of these pictures in comic over
there again
now the new nets the beam ants don't use
lanes anymore I'm sorry that should be a
lot smarter
Yeah right now now it's starting to get
a little shade
this is a good answer to whether you
know this is a gradual yeah it's not
it's not something that we're still
engaged we are self driving cars is that
even a good question
what leader self-driving cars
I don't make 19 ever calls I make
self-driving cars
that's right yo tell you about
they're not real tell you about we real
hey everyone I guess you super cruise
cruising no I can tell you know ain't no
babe to do some work of smoke
Kruse
TM engineers a wicked median if you go
to Detroit apparently goodbye pandas if
they want they can go to our site right
now no reason we brought it bought a
neon I think we should out them yeah not
specifically their name just their
company no nothing not the person's name
who recently born Leon was the Palo Alto
Innovation Center of Ford will get
around ship in their yard never stopping
Canales and so exciting not just for
food or drinks but we're also hosting a
meet up at make Salt Lake it's the
makerspace in downtown Salt Lake City
Arena pieces those will have pizza in
here for you there's another event
happening so their parking might be a
little tough in the lot but yeah those
people out there watching from Salt Lake
we're coming to you
Chicago is also TBD we've really gotta
see how these young we got we got the
four on the schedule check out the
medium post if you were more about
though
or the back of the shirt or the back of
the shirt yeah yeah we're gonna be there
at 7:00 absolutely sir the demerger the
meetup is still happening is that make
it what depending on unless there's a
line to get into the trade Salt Lake oh
yeah we're best four o'clock somewhere
like here o'clock somewhere backing
Black Rose okay salt lake in the GPS
Black Rock Salt Lake where we'll wait
can we fix ways that I sir just actually
as long as you turn off radar cruise
under Toyota should actually be on so
you have to press this button on the
front of the stock as long as it's off
its gonna drop some warnings down like
late departure of our malfunction but
that's okay
when the young boots back up you'll see
those warnings go right what we advise
you to not do is turn the car off and on
while you are driving that is a bad idea
yeah but this is some people used to do
that some people used to do that do not
encourage that
is not great good thing we left that
radar we left that radar moving in
Yeah right yeah
don't turn your car off on your drive in
the acura you can't turn it back on this
thing were you're rolling with no brakes
and no no power brakes and no power
steering you have some rights to it
all right where are we way seated all
right let's weigh somewhere let's check
out with a black rock
salt lake is how far it is Black Rock
lady - the way to do at work
Yunel support USA roads no no we don't
support left roads
you should lobby your governments to
change my rock salt lake work is it free
I just heard that was a good spot he's
afraid
what
sound
that's a good way to type on Yuri honest
the rest earn and here I always thought
don't put your hand in front of the
camera no this is good yeah black mark
Microsystems I can't find the one that
talked about but the the Great Salt Lake
State Park was pretty good
all right there check if it's free no
it's gotta be free man we haven't made
any money yet on this two of a million
pounds you know what if we sell out
tonight let's just just the car old
Great Salt Lake
State Park oh it's a statement good I
support today but you don't look too
really tiny so yeah it's right next to
Great Salt Lake State Park I should
actually drive
[Music]
we'll still at least one yawn tonight
cool yeah you find an awesome cool mo
128 and 64 128 but you get choice
because you are yes Wow
actually you're gonna be the first
person to get in the yawn oh yeah that's
you yeah that's something anything yeah
they haven't
[Music]
i love i'm tributing the yeah but we've
been contributing all the police back to
its calling out the five oh yeah we want
to get on local you talk radio shows oh
yeah we do to call in we could do that
good call right sir i got i got four we
would call in from the car yeah I mean I
could I got a drive this is treacherous
it's late we're seeing it all compiled I
can say it's
that's pretty conferencing
with the reboot and then engages and
then I work all this we finally got
updates - yeah we probably got whatever
whatever are they upset recorders it's
driving okay just like
see ya don't want to go eight
[Music]
it's close it is actually driving fine
it is looking out the tracks are way
more to the right then final count of
eons was 111 we have a lemon with us o
final kind of shifty literally what we
had left over well actually that's not
true how many years do we have in the
car
no sale you're not even driving the
wrong place that's it is generally when
you're driving these sort of conditions
you want to drive in other people's
tracks yeah
even if it's wrong even if it's like not
the center of the lane yeah can I have
two so this is something that like
peanuts are gonna fix our new machine
learning models are not going to rely on
lanes anymore and they should be smart
enough to understand like even this kind
of driving which is really important
something like the rules they can
understand no no that's just one
well it's not yeah it's know it man it's
gonna let's go so I'm gonna saw you get
those snowballs at each other so I get
it close yeah I don't have a cone I
don't have a coat she live in Salt Lake
you're coming to the meat salt lake
let's hope we make money tonight yo this
is like going on tour man I wanna make
technology cool Lake City is pretty dry
downtown that's good news
I really got live updates she passed
these people or the tutor it's to tread
it doesn't matter so yeah its sixth we
can barely see
how many are about 45 what's on the box
well sorry yeah well certainly the card
or the box whichever they prefer hey
borrows knives I'm sitting next to a
truck
so we think
don't know how slippery this road is I
haven't driven this car a lot so I don't
need to know like what the traction
limits well also we don't really have
this weather in California so
no it's not like I was fine in the snow
we didn't get my Benz because I driven
it and snow so much like I knew exactly
you know when the traction control was
gonna fire like the limit to the car
ones I've never even been in the car
this car
because better look even better
the thing is given know well it works
with the person right like it's a driver
assistance feature you still know how to
work yeah yeah
clubs are just like yeah just that you
know I we don't recommend using a pilot
in conditions where the road isn't read
on't have good grip on the road just
like you wouldn't use cruise control of
the snow
when there's access no longer obviously
if it's like raining folks you need to
eat vegetables okay this is important
yeah this too it is important is for
vegetables how many miles of autonomous
driving every logged on this trip yeah
we can conglomerated GPS give a
percentage
[Music]
in some parts of Nevada we were a little
disappointed because the lane
Utah was really good until we have this
snow it's almost like a hundred we can
get a cheap jacket at flying jets before
Salt Lake oh wait Salt Lake dude let's
go do a job of flight J let's go fight a
nice thank-you for they're definitely
going to find J
it's eally car right now
is not engaged
- no my best with the radar this is this
is good testing
gender says $20 on selling out by that
issue
I don't like them doesn't have a big car
which some of my dad drive feedback EDM
periscoping yeah for them drivers you
got burglars at our East
well right now yeah I'm not seeing Ali a
car it's also letting me engage so what
it should do in this scenario is it's
hard to find healthy food along the road
last night we saw daddy's actually
kicked up their health many a little bit
Oh daddy's was dead easy just hobnob we
were to a Denny's in California it was
great no open belly cannot read that
road signs like speed limit aren't you
quite dessert how I guess a week all
right
are we getting any radar packets
actually if the guys are home just ssh
into this phone and see if we're getting
greater care messages yeah
yeah so this is 0.4 so about 0.4 we
talked about in the first periscope
someone says 34 so one says radar in
their Honda works great in snow
yeah the snow might be really say
initials
yes
[Music]
come for me from Salt Lake
that way though that ways you should've
worked
forty minutes not fixed
it's got bugs fix that bugs
so pouty 0.4
on this road trip we're debugging we're
recording all the logs back to
headquarters get a little fix
I'm flying just great yeah let's get a
coat and let's get a CB radio like I'm
not kidding
my CB radio doctor truckers man
there's the coming I demonstration you
in a coordinate YJ probably will try to
periscope able to make Salt Lake